[
  {
    "question": "sit",
    "answer": "sat"
  },
  {
    "question": "speak",
    "answer": "spoken"
  },
  {
    "question": "lie",
    "answer": "lain"
  },
  {
    "question": "lead",
    "answer": "led"
  },
  {
    "question": "read",
    "answer": "read"
  },
  {
    "question": "grow",
    "answer": "grown"
  },
  {
    "question": "lose",
    "answer": "lost"
  },
  {
    "question": "fall",
    "answer": "fallen"
  },
  {
    "question": "send",
    "answer": "sent"
  },
  {
    "question": "build",
    "answer": "built"
  },
  {
    "question": "understand",
    "answer": "understood"
  },
  {
    "question": "draw",
    "answer": "drawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "break",
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "question": "spend",
    "answer": "spent"
  },
  {
    "question": "cut",
    "answer": "cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "rise",
    "answer": "risen"
  },
  {
    "question": "drive",
    "answer": "driven"
  },
  {
    "question": "buy",
    "answer": "bought"
  },
  {
    "question": "wear",
    "answer": "worn"
  },
  {
    "question": "choose",
    "answer": "chosen"
  }
]
